Chapter 3: Combat Commentators Part I

" Hello everyone. Welcome to the unofficial final of the year. " Lee's cheerful voice announced to an energetic Sunday morning crowd of the stadium.

"Both Ravenclaw and Slytherin are ruling the point charts without any contention.

Ravenclaw comes to this match boasting of its Star Chaser Captain Davies, who has made a fine art of beating all the defenses of the opposite team. In previous match with Hufflepuff, he forced their chasers too to play the defense positions yet there was no stopping him or his goal rate.

Slytherin captain Flint has to take that almost as a personal insult. Since he and his entire 'chaser' team are coming to this match with a score of 0 against Gryffindor in previous match. In fact with Weasley Brothers' general mayhem and with Super Keeper Wood's near perfect defense, the only reason that Gryffindor isn't clean sweeping the opposition is because they can't find a seeker decent enough to catch a snitch if it were the size of quaffle.

But we can stop thinking about that right now. Ravenclaw and Slytherin can start making all the noise for their teams.

And Hufflepuff and Gryffindors can cheer up as well since today is the only game day of the season when their team won't loose.

All those things aside get ready folks. Both teams are here and so is Madam Hooch. The show is about to begin."

A snitch fluttered and disappeared. 14 players flew in a blur of speed and a roar of cheers made the stadium shiver with anticipation. Everybody's eyes were on the sky.

Almost.

If somebody would have paid notice, they might have seen students do something they do only during class time; whisper. But nobody was noticing.

Lee continued " And yes. The game has immediately turned to a personal grudge match between the two captains. Marcus flint is in the possession of the quaffle and flying away towards the goalpost.

Breathing down his broomstick is Davies. Flint is now trying to shake him off, and he looses Davies. He has a clear angle at the goals now, defense is coming now to intercept, but they won't be in time. He is going to score.

Woah. Defended.

Davies shows unbelievable reflexes and steals the quaffle from midflight flying backwards.

Now he is speeding full speed towards the goal post on the other end.

He dodges the bludgers, another chaser homes in on him. And Davies passes.

He passes to Andrew who has a clear shot.

And he Scores!"

Lee's voice boomed loud in the stadium. A bit too loud.

Usually his voice was drowned in the cheers that immediately followed. Yet, the cheers this time were dispersed.

The near silence that followed the goal was most audible. Even the players stopped for a second in mid air. If snitch would have stopped and hovered at one spot at that time, both the seekers would have missed it.

Lee looked around to his Head of the House who was always there, ready to snatch away the mike the moment it was necessary. (And with Lee, it often was)

McGonagall too could sense it. There was something strange going on. She walked over to some students nearby who seemed to be more interested in a book rather than the game. She had often chided her students for playing games in the class when they should have been reading. It seemed slightly insane to her as she now asked the students to hand over the book and pay more attention to the game.

But she did confiscate it and then as she couldn't help but be curious, she opened the book.

Chapter 5: Divination Part I

" How could you?" McGonagall asked Harry who was once again in her office. Draco, or Eiji, was being questioned by Severus Snape separately.

"By a combo of Muffliato and Ventriliquo" Harry replied.

"What?" McGonagall's confusion was instinctive.

"That's how I overtook the commentary from Lee. I thought you would be happy that I stopped him" Harry tried to sound equally confused.

"I don't care about that. How did you predict the results?" McGonagall said.

"Not that again." Harry sighed. "You suspect that I have used the Time Turner, don't you? This is getting to be repetitive"

"Haven't you? How else could you have predicted every single point?" McGonagall asked.

There was silence.

"Harry?" McGonagall asked again.

" Is it too far fetched to believe that somebody could have made those predictions? Even after reading all the reasons I provided, all the strategic outcomes I outlined?" Harry asked.

" It is a bit far fetched that a first year student who has never played the game before, never even bothered to see a single match until today would suddenly be able to predict the score. It was like you had learned divination."

"Definition is the true divination." Harry said.

McGonagall stopped. She stopped because she understood. Some part of her brain wasn't going to be the same again.

"The great muggle economist Adam Smith talked about mankind when they had not invented compass.

Imagine the people living near the sea shore, seeing that great wide length in front of themselves and not being able to go beyond the horizon of their eyesight. Forever afraid of what may be beyond, afraid of falling off the edge of the flat world they 'knew' themselves to be living in.

But when the definition of the world was changed for better, painstakingly, bit by bit, voyage by voyage, we found out the sphere and filled in the blanks . It became simple to see far beyond what just eyes could.

By defining their world, they were able to divine their position in it. "

"But Mr. Potter" McGonagall said " I may not know much about definition, but thanks to a dear colleague of mine, I do know things about divination.

A map of the world is still not the world.

You may be able to say it roughly where you would land if you follow a particular path. But there is a limit to that possibility.

Divination is a rather imprecise branch of magic. The best seers may not have been able to predict the match point by point as you did.

So while your definition, or should I say your 'map drawing' may be excellent, I still do not believe that you predicted every single point of the game with just reasoning. "

"So you are going to check me for time turner use, even if you don't have any proof. Just like the last time when you didn't find anything?"

"You do have a record of breaking rules Harry"

"What rule have I broken in this incident?"

"Well, the rules you break are usually the ones that nobody has written as yet. I guess that's because there aren't many people who imagine up the offenses that you do."

"But if its not written, then how does it become a rule?"

"Ok, fine. You did break the rule of interrupting the match. You broke into school system of commentary. That is an obvious violation. "

"That was the first thing I talked about. Remember? I told you how I used Muffliato and Ventriliquo to take over the commentary. Then you expressly said that you didn't care about that.

So if you base your inquiry on that, it would just be a hypocrisy."

"You seem like you are desperate to hide something."

"Either 'hide' or 'protect'. In this instance, it would be protecting my rights to not be unduly harassed.

Just by being in authority, you get to question me anytime you want. If on any occasion, I am wrong then there are huge penalties to pay. Yet, if you are wrong, then there are absolutely no consequences.

Why should I be the only one with something at stake? "

"You think it doesn't pain me to doubt you again and again?"

" Does it pain the headmaster?"

"How is that relevant?"

"Who ordered you to interrogate me right now?"

McGonagall didn't reply. Harry knew she wouldn't. She had always had doubt about Headmaster's intentions. And she was honest. Defining her was equivalent to divining her. That part of Harry's arguments was not a strategy, but a truth.

After a moment of mutual silence, Harry said what he wanted to.

"Fine. I will agree to take the Time Turner test.

But on a condition"

"What?" McGonagall was surprised by both the acceptance and the demand.

"A condition." Harry said "And I will tell the condition only after Headmaster permits it. "

He looked at the creases on her face getting more crumpled. She was considering a negative reply.

"Won't it be a fair thing to do professor?" Harry added. If bringing up the concept of 'Fairness' didn't work on McGonagall, then his hope was already gone.

McGonagall's wrinkles ceased compressing further. Harry knew that he had succeeded in convincing her.

Chapter 6: Divination Part II

They reached the end of the spiral that led to Dumbledore's office. And then the gate opened to release a shout.

" He Abused me. He was terrible. Asked everybody to give me more food. Can you imagine?" A furious Derrick was shouting at Dumbledore. Harry wondered how he got the meeting with Dumbledore. Maybe he just shouted his way in .

" But my dear Derrick, that is quite terrible" Dumbledore remarked. " You should take strong steps against it.

How about protesting with a hunger strike?"

Harry suppressed laughter. McGonogall wasn't finding anything funny here. When she spoke, Harry noticed she actually seemed concerned about Derrick. It was perhaps only fair. Perhaps even Derrick didn't yet deserve a conversation alone with Dumbledore.

"Headmaster", she said to divert the conversation and Harry distinctly noticed her throwing a kind and concerned look toward Derrick " There is a matter that we need to discuss about Harry, he.."

At mention of Harry's name, Derrick turned in his chair.

"You." Derrick thundered.

" You noticed just now?" Harry said " No wonder you are not a seeker."

Derrick stood up.

"You think you are funny. " Derrick said while walking towards Harry. " Have you forgotten already what I did to you in Quirell's class?"

Derrick stood a shove's distance away from Harry. His eyes locked on Harry's eyes from above.

On the side, McGonagall's concern for Derrick suddenly increased multifold. First coming to Dumbledore's office alone with a complaint and then directly threatening Harry, Derrick certainly was courting trouble with all his heart. "Derrick" she said "Are you.."

Harry could sense some of the surprise in McGonagall's voice. He completed the sentence for her.

"Yes Professor." He said out aloud "He is as thick mentally as he is physically."

"Harry!" McGonagall exclaimed with fury.

Part of Harry did feel appreciation for her. Her current fury was more intense than when she was talking about wrong use of time turner. She was really concerned about Derrick. She was concerned even if Derrick had been a bully for years. She would have punished him most severely if she ever found him guilty. But she wouldn't let that be a biasing factor. She wouldn't let even a bully be bullied.

But, Harry couldn't stop now. He had to bully Derrick a bit more. It was an unexpected development to find him in Dumbledore's office. But now that he was here, it was much easier to move directly to the aim of the whole setup. The perfect opportunity to successfully conclude the first step to overturn the absorption of Dragon and Sunshine armies.

Meanwhile Derrick has had too much. Harry after all had made sure that Derrick should have too much.

" I challenge you" Derrick said, cutting Prof. McGonagall's outburst " I challenge you to a duel?"

"A challenge? Of what?" Harry asked " The only two things you are remotely good at are eating and playing Quidditch. But then you would be afraid of a Quidditch match since you might be defeated by first years. How about a pudding eating contest instead? Let the whole Hogwarts know that you have a moleskin pouch for a stomach." Harry helpfully suggested.

Derrick seemed to be pumping himself wider with breath. This was not good. He was supposed to reply here. Harry asked himself if he had made the proper reply too obscure for Derrick.

Fine, he will make it more obvious with an additional insult.

"Yeah, amongst Quidditch and Eating matches, that's what you ought to choose." Harry continued "The increased width from the contest may help you defend all the three goalposts at once."

" That's it. " Derrick finally found words " I challenge you to a Quidditch match. I would settle for nothing less than humiliating you on the same ground as you humiliated me. It's only fair."

He of course didn't realize that the words that he found were the ones that Harry made him find. He didn't realize that he had started with a challenge of a duel, a wizarding duel, and ended with a Quidditch challenge in stead. He just noticed that he finally had some sort of a victory. So he turned to Headmaster with hope that the permission would be granted.

"Sir, please allow us to have a Quidditch match" Derrick said.

"This can't be allowed." McGonagall said from the side. "None of the first years even play Quidditch. They might be hurt. The idea is insane."

Harry smiled. Things were going according to plan. McGonagall calling an idea insane was a sure sign that Dumbledore would whole-heartedly champion it.

"But Professor" Harry said aloud, addressing McGonagall " Headmaster already approves of this.

He has already approved of the Inter Year Wars in the defense against dark arts classes.

So doesn't that mean that he wants the first year students to break the age barriers."

McGonagall suddenly stopped protesting. She could now see what the whole thing was about. She had been around Dumbledore for too long to not spot a plot in its climax. This was the condition Harry wanted in exchange for the time turner test, condition to challenge the Inter Year War conditions, and now with Derrick being here, he didn't even need to take the test.

Harry continued his appeal to Dumbledore.

"And after all. If a Hero faces a challenge that seems to be beyond him, can he possibly shy away from it?" Harry concluded.

Yup, everything going smooth according to the plan.

Dumbledore laughed.

That was never a good sign. Harry's heart and mind started to race faster just a little bit.

" Minerva. " he said " what was it that you brought Harry in my office for?"

" It was, .. " McGonagall said or tried to " It was on account of the sensitive matter. But I guess we should talk about it later."

"But Minerva, there is no need." Dumbledore said. " I believe Mr. Potter did not breach your instructions on the matter. In fact if I am not wrong, he would have most likely agreed to take the test, but with some condition.

Am I mistaken on that Minerva?"

McGonagall was trying to understand how Dumbledore already knew the outcome of their meeting. She nodded in affirmative.

Harry meanwhile was just reminding himself why Dumbledore laughing was always ominous.

" I had told her earlier that she could question you on the matter but that it would be unnecessary, Harry." Dumbledore addressed him " For you see. I do believe in you."

Harry was surprised for a second.

" And when I say I believe in you" Dumbledore continued, " I mean that at the very least I believe in your lack of guilt, if not innocence."

Harry wasn't surprised any more.

Derrick was looking back and forth as if to try and find subtitles for this conversation.

" And regarding the permission that the two of you seek…" he said looking at Derrick "..well there it is."

A knock came on the open door at that precise moment. Derrick instinctively looked around.

Oliver Wood, Marcus Flint, Roger Davies and Cedric Diggory entered the Headmaster's chambers.

Harry felt a chill. Dumbledore really had foreseen Harry's motive.

" You called us Professor?" Oliver asked.

"Yes, I did." Dumbledore pleasantly replied. " You see I was saying that I believe that things could be predicted. So I predicted that you would be here at this time."

"But professor" Wood calmly replied " You knew that we would be here. You asked us to be here at this time, remember?"

" But I asked you to be here because you were going to be here. " Dumbledore said in a tone that implied that he was imparting unprecedented wisdom on every single being on the planet with this one sentence.

Even Derrick could sense that there was something mad about Dumbledore.

" I hope one day you will all understand that."

5 people in the room passionately hoped that such a day would never come.

" But what you can understand today, " Dumbledore said " is that you are here because you are Captains of your Quidditch team as well as the generals of your armies. Thus due to an agreement between Harry and Derrick, your presence would be desirable in a Quidditch match. If you all agree, you can move to the office of Madam Hooch later on and she will give you further instructions.

I think with the 5 of you, all the positions in the team would be determined except the position of beaters. Assuming of course that Mr. Derrick chooses to return to his previous position of chaser. Thus theoretically, Madam Hooch will choose the beaters, it would seem that the result is currently unpredictable.

But is it?

Is there anybody who really can't predict who those two beaters would be?" He said. And now he was talking directly to Harry " That's what I mean when I say I believe in your 'lack of guilt'. Certain things are not only predictable but inevitable. Aren't they Harry."

Dumbledore said and then started to look at the door.

Things had gone smooth till now. Dumbledore had agreed and also involved the army generals in the Quidditch team. This was just what Harry wanted. But why was Harry getting what he wanted before he could ask it. Just how far has Dumbledore seen his plan. The answer, Harry felt, would be walking soon through the door that Dumbledore was looking at.

A knock that people knew would be heard was in deed heard, Zabini and Bulstrode entered.

Harry felt like he was hit. His complete plan was figured out. Dumbledore didn't just know that Harry had used time turner, but he knew the exact method.

"Please come in" Dumbledore said. " But I am afraid that you aren't supposed to be here."

" But" Zabini said with some hesitation " you were the one who asked us to be here at this precise time. "

" I asked you because you would have been here anyway, but now that you are here, I have to tell you that there was no particular need."

Everybody in the room looked at Zabini and Bulstrode with sympathy in their eyes. They wanted to tell them that Dumbledore's insanity is universal and shouldn't be taken personally. Though that wouldn't have been much help either.

Harry however could clearly listen to the warning being issued to him by Dumbledore. Was this how it was? Did Dumbledore always said things so that it would make sense only to one person whose secret plot was being destroyed? Was that why he sounded insane to everyone else who had no idea about the situation they were in?

Dumbledore continued pleasantly " And this mistake is of course what I meant when I was talking about lack of guilt as well as lack of innocence. " Dumbledore said looking to Harry.

Harry didn't or couldn't say anything back.

"I guess that concludes it. Inter year wars are on hold. The fate of it shall be decided by a Quidditch match that shall be held one month from now." Dumbledore said " Unless of course anybody else here wants to challenge anybody else. This time I will get to decide the method of contest."

A cold shudder went through collective consciousness of the room.

McGonagall came to her senses first.

" Now get moving all of you." She said to her students gently nudging them to the direction of the door. " It is lunch time already, and you must be terribly hungry."

She instantly regretted her words as she found Derrick turning to her with deep hurt in his eyes.

Harry despite himself couldn't help but laugh.

Chapter 7: Divination Part III

"Harry" Zabini whispered to Harry.

Others left for the great Hall for lunch. Bulstrode traveled the fastest to outrun the breaking gossip of an Inter Year Quidditch match. She had to. After all with her time turner recently limited to 6 hours she didn't have much room to spare that day after a busy match.

Zabini thus continued whispering even if they were now alone " What was that all about? Did Dumbledore know about us taking the bets on Quidditch match?"

Harry looked at Zabini. His obvious attempts to mix an accusation with a question was almost cute.

" You mean to say that does Dumbledore know that you take bets on a Quidditch match. That you have been taking the bets this entire season, and have been making sure that students here have much lesser pocket money. " Harry replied.

" You say as if you disapprove Harry. You were the one who gave me the idea of taking the whole thing to Floo book. You showed me how to do it, how to have people commit the amount in writing and make sure that curses would fire on them if they breach the contract.

You even told me exactly what bets to make.

And boy was it a good business. No more betting on the winner and looser only. One can bet for every single point. Funny thing is that whole thing is addictive. The more the people bet, the more they want to bet."

"Of course. " Harry suppressed his detest for Gambling and Zabini's delight over people's addiction. He continued in plain conversational tone "But the thing is that Dumbledore knows about the whole thing now, so you should close it as soon as possible."

Harry started to walk away.

" You can't just walk off like this." Zabini called behind him. " You are involved in this too. If Dumbledore knows about this then you have to figure out how to get him off this."

Harry continued to walk, only change was that he was laughing now.

" I know why you helped me with betting" Zabini said.

Harry stopped.

" It is not a coincidence that you just came up to me and helped me make bets and then went on to predict the entire game. Is it?" Zabini continued.

Harry turned back

" You aren't into gambling or Quidditch. You just took the whole data from bets and saw who was the favorite. Maybe applied some muggle science or something on it. "

Harry relaxed. So Zabini didn't really know about what had happened. He was just guessing.

" I will tell Dumbledore the whole story. You wouldn't want that would you?"

One day Zabini would grow up to be a fine example of slytherin manipulator. Currently though he was just a kid. Harry couldn't even feel proper anger towards him.

" I wouldn't want that, would I?" Harry said " Let me see. I told you how to use Floo Book properly and wrote a couple of bets for you.

Did I ever ask you to make the bets?"

"Of course, you clearly said that I could do whatever I want with it." Zabini said and then stopped.

" You realize already.

What I did could have just been an exercise in studying probability.

What you did was not only rule breaking, it might as well as have been a crime." Harry bluffed. He didn't know the legal stand of magical world on betting, but with Zabini, he didn't need to get serious, he could just play around.

"So while I may be questioned and mildly chided by McGonagall, you may find that your wand is being snapped in two and you are joining Hagrid in his hut as an assistant to keep watch on the monsters in the Forbidden Forest.

So I don't think you want to do what you said you want to do, unless you also want to spend the rest of your life trying to double cross an Aragog." Harry said.

Zabini didn't know what an Aragog was, but he was sure that he didn't want to know either.

"But then again" Harry said " You do like to shoot yourself.

So by all means, do tell Dumbledore ."

And Harry walked away this time with no interruption from Zabini who was holding on tight to his unsnapped wand.

...

The lunch was already over by the time Harry reached the Great hall. He moved on towards the Ravenclaw dormitory.

He was facing the portrait of the Ravenclaw lady that nobody seemed to know the name of. She was much like her riddles that one had to answer to gain entrance.

She smiled at him when she saw him approach. " If a war's outcome is known beforehand then is it worth fighting?" She asked.

That was rather topical. Where did she get her questions? Did she know somehow what happens in the castle and make a question based on that?

"No war's outcome is ever known before it is fought." Harry answered with a slight guilt in his voice. Harry wondered if he really believed in that answer.

"Correct young Raven. You may now enter".

The door opened. Harry entered the common room.

All the activity in the room came to a stop.

Of course they all knew about the forthcoming Quidditch match, Harry thought. One could count on Milicent Bulstrode to spread the word. She might have even used the remaining limit of her time turner after she had used it to place the correct bets on morning's Quidditch match.

She got them all correct. Not even a bluff or two to make it look normal. And she had been doing it all season.

So to know the scores, all Harry had to do was to organize the bets of Zabini on the point level, had to tell him to place bets not only on the winner and loser, but for every single goal scored. That and a little hacking in the Floo Book to check whom did Bulstrode bet upon, and he knew the entire result before hand without even using his time turner.

It went rather well, except that Dumbledore seemed to have figured it all out. A real problem.

But Harry didn't get time to think on it.

The intensity of the gazes in the room thickened as Ravenclaw Quidditch Captain Roger Davies approached Harry.

" Harry, we know why you did it." Roger said " We were uncomfortable too with involuntary absorption of Sunshine and Dragon army. "

" I appreciate your candour captain." Harry replied. " I would have expected nothing less from a Ravenclaw."

"And I would expect nothing less than your trademark brilliance on the Quidditch field Harry. Your commentary today was excellent. Let's see if you can match the results on the field as well.

May the best team win." Roger said extending his hand.

" May the best team win " Harry replied and shook Roger's hand.

Ravenclaw house burst with cheer. The game was on.

Chapter 8: Friendly Fire

Harry walked along the corridor, already playing the Quidditch match in his head that others will be playing one month later. A voice behind him bludgered those thoughts away.

"Hey Harry"
Harry turned with a start. The corridor was supposed to be empty, so when did Fred come behind him?
"Hey Harry"
Harry re turned with a fresh start. Now George was standing on the opposite side.

How did they sneak in? Invisibility cloak, unlikely, one was rare enough, two would be outside any decent probability. Disillusionment charm? No, too advanced. If Weasley twins knew it, Hogwarts would be a war zone by now. But, then.. Ah, of course.

Harry sidestepped and looked down. Fred and George were still standing with one foot on their broom. They must have been practicing outside in the grounds and flied in when they saw Harry crossing the corridor.

"Nice flying." Harry said " I didn't even hear you land. Madam Hooch should definitely pick you up for the senior team. Or have you been already picked and came to tell me the obvious?"

"Harry" George sighed "Harry, Harry" Fred continued and concluded.
"This feels all wrong. Its almost like in any reality we should have been playing from the same side."
"But you know us. If it's wrong we have got to do it."
"Matter of principle you see. So don't take it personally when we come after you in this match."
"For we will come after you. We will be ignoring everyone else just to get to you."
"You better make it fun. Don't be crushed too easily."
"From now on, it's a war."
"No hard feelings then"

The pure glee of malice on the twins' faces was a sight of marvel. It was rare to see so much happiness on a human face. Harry had trouble for a moment paying attention to the actual declaration of war.
" Are you sure guys?" Harry asked them." For I will pull no punches either if you are declaring war."

"This is Quidditch Harry. You might be a good flier, you may even understand the theory of it better than anybody else but you have never yet played this game."
"So the question is are you sure?"

Harry looked at both of them. This was going to be more fun than expected. He should really be thanking Professor Quirell for his brilliant injustice later on.

"No. The real question is.." Harry said ".. do you know that a broom can listen."

"What?" Fred and George said together. How did this even relate to the conversation?

"There are two ways to give command to a broom. One is by weight shifting, which we do while flying. And the other one is by voice commands. Like when we say 'up' to mount the broom and the broom listens if we really mean it."

" Of course we know it. This is the first thing taught in flying sessions"
"So?"

"So" Harry replied with an evil grin that made him look like the third twin. " I can do this"

To Weasley twins it all seemed to have happened in a slow motion. Harry extended both his arms looking like some evil muggle messiah and then said in a calm booming voice. " Up!"

Two brooms flew from under the twins. The twins spun once in the air like vertical tops. A beautiful hyperbole was formed with their curved backs, just for a second. And then two thuds, travelling faster than an echo, ended the sudden slow motion for the twins who were on the ground.

Both brooms were now tucked in Harry's hand. The war so far wasn't going good for the twins and a look at Harry's grin, as seen from the ground, made them sure that it hasn't ended yet.

He walked over to the middle and placed the brooms in the air above twins.

"Down." He slowly said.

Twins didn't know there was a 'down' command too. They never checked it. Did anybody?

But they couldn't think further about it as their own brooms came down slowly and started to press against them.

"Now they can't land" Harry said "because you are in the way, so not knowing what else to do they will keep pressing. At the same time, you can't move away because they won't stop pressing. Its something called deadlock.

Nice name, right?"

And with that Harry walked away and twins heard him singing a song as he went:

"War! huh-yeah
What is it good for?
Absolutely nothing
Uh-huh"

-

The sound of the song slowly faded and Twins began to escape from their own brooms inch by inch.
"Catchy tune, huh." George said.
"We knew something like this might happen. Its ok, this had to be done." Fred said from under his own broom as he tried to move further sideways.
"Of course." George agreed, "Who wanted a friendly match."
They finally inched their way out from under their pressing brooms. The brooms finally landed and became inactive. Both stood together looking in the direction Harry had just gone.

"We won't let you destroy Quidditch that easily. Because 'War', dear Harry.."George said
" ..means nothing unless it means everything." Concluded Fred.

Chapter 11: Asimov's One and Half Laws Part I

Later that night:

" We are using him for our practice?" Hermione asked in a voice that almost rose to a shriek.

" Hermione, I know you might have problem with this. So I thought that let's clear both our positions on the matter in his presence.

I believe that whoever designed them is extremely evil. But now they have been designed that way I don't think there is much we can do.

So if you have problem with us using Dobby for practice, you must tell what can we do about him." Harry calmly replied.

" You really believe that his condition can't be changed?" Hermione asked.

"Hermione, it's like they have been hardwired to follow the orders. What do you think you are going to do now?

Give him a Godel-esque command 'I order you not to follow orders?'" Harry said and then stopped.

It was like a sudden thought wiped out every other reality for him.

" Actually it's a rather good idea, don't you think. I'll try it right now."

"Stop" Hermione's voice was now an actual shriek. " You are giving him an 'order' Harry, not a 'command', its not that innocent, he is not a computer program. And even a computer program would crash on that one. What do you want to do to Dobby, drive him insane?"

"Relax. I wasn't directly going to give him Godel command. I would have tried other things first. And even then I would have modified the final command to " I order you to not follow any further orders until they are in your interest", or something similar. That won't crash a program, would it?" Harry asked.

" I repeat Harry, he is not a program." Hermione said in a calm and firm tone.

" Well magical creatures are created with certain fixed rules, so his behaviour would be somewhat similar to a program. How about we start with simple commands, I mean orders" Harry corrected himself as he saw the look on Hermione's face "..and see how he reacts to it. We will come to know if he can actually be helped or not."

Hermione took a moment to think that over. Harry took that to mean that she had no issue.

"Great. I will be giving him a complex set of commands to check how he handles the data. So first let's check whether he follows order list in FIFO or LIFO." He said and then continued talking to Dobby " Dobby, I am going to give you two commands right now. Start following them only when I have given you both the commands. Ok?"

Dobby looked at both of them and nodded. He felt strange that people were asking him whether or not it was ok to give an order.

Hermione meanwhile was immersed in seeing what was going on. She had even stopped trying to correct Harry's use of 'command' back to 'order'.

" First command is" Harry said, " that you should not follow my second command.

My second command is that you go and sit on that chair." Harry said and pointed to a chair.

Dobby stood blinking. He did nothing.

" Great, now let's reverse it. I am again going to give you two commands. Follow them only after I have given both the commands.

My first command is to go sit on that chair and my second command is to not follow my first command. "

Dobby moved and sat on the chair that was pointed at.

And then, he suddenly looked possessed as the time to fulfill the second order came.

"Harry!" Hermione shouted as both of them rushed towards him. Dobby was not the docile, cute-ugly creature that they were with just a moment ago.

No longer he was blinks, wide eyes and eagerness.

He was rage, madness and guilt.

He took the chair and tried to hit himself with it. Harry and Hermione tried to stop him from doing so , but their combined physical effort didn't contain Dobby's self destruction streak.

Dobby found the chair to be too light, so he rushed to a wall. And started to bang his head.

He is a head banger on rock now. Harry observed. What has happened to my sense of humor, he then questioned.

"Stop!" He shouted.

Dobby stopped.

Hermione rushed towards him to examine him "Are you ok? Are you hurt in anyway? Should we take you to Madam Pomfrey?"

Dobby was apparently ok. He was stopped just in time.

"Great." Harry said, "So you follow FIFO then.

Now, are you ready to move on with next command chain?"

"What do you mean by next command chain?" Hermione interrupted. She was determined that there wasn't going to be any more 'command', let alone a 'chain'.

"You are the one who wants to change him Hermione.

Do you now see what that process or even attempt would mean to him?" Harry asked. "And after all that I am still not sure if he would be able to change his hardwired instructions; the primary magic of a house-elf's creation."

Hermione was breathing anger.

"Change may be always painful Harry but that doesn't mean that the pain has to be made beyond endurance.

Your approach isn't the only approach to try and change him.

In fact, this is not even your approach." Hermione said.

" Not my approach? Then whose is it?" Harry asked.

" Professor Quirrell's."

"What?"

"You are doing the same thing to Dobby that Prof. Quirell did to you in the class when he asked Derrick and others to push you around. "

"That was.." Harry protested.

"That was beyond excuse." Hermione replied. " The only reason Professor Quirell got away with it, the only reason Dumbledore didn't fire him or did something worse than firing, the only reason that entire Ravenclaw or at least I didn't jump in to stop that class was because of you.

Because you consented. Because you were convinced it was good for you. Because you showed us that you could endure that concentrated pain of growing up.

But apparently we were wrong. Apparently that pain was in deed beyond you.

Or you wouldn't have tried to do the same thing to Dobby. "

" Hermione. You are just being too sensitive. Look at him; Dobby is ok. Totally unharmed.

If anything at all I was just trying to do the same thing as you, trying to see if he could be freed of his servitude.

You are angry because you have just seen what your efforts would lead to." Harry calmly replied.

Hermione looked at him, her fury now cold.

" Dobby" she said to the elf ".. come with me. We are getting out of here." And with a regal air she walked out of the classroom.

Dobby followed Hermione out of the door. Just before the door closed, he looked at Harry. And then the door closed shut.

" 'Dobby, come with me.'" Harry mimicked Hermione's words that echoed in that empty classroom " So when it suits her, then she is ok with commanding house elves."

Chapter 14: Fosbury Flop

Game day..

" Good morning fellow Quidditch Crazies.

Welcome to the game that is already the most remarkable Quidditch game ever played, even before the opening whistle has been blown.

We have on one side the greatest team of Hogwarts. With Wood the super keeper, Weasley twins who together are the synonym of mayhem, Roger Davies with his precise aggression, Marcus Flint with his aggressive aggression, Cedric Diggory who has such a good record that some people have started suspecting that he is not a 'seeker' but a 'seer'.

Oh yeah, and Derrick too, who has gone back to his original role of Chaser for this match. Some players have contested his inclusion in this team, but well he has in a way made this match possible, and make no mistake when it comes to Quidditch he is no pushover but very much a, ahem, heavyweight.

On the other side, we have perhaps the most interesting team of Hogwarts.

Harry, Draco, Hermione, Neville, Padma, Parvati and Goyle. None of whom have ever played a match.

And yet, if that betting site that came on Floo Book would have been still active, I am willing to bet that there would have been plenty of folks here betting on the victory of the first year team. It might have been tough to even tell if they would have been the underdogs or the favorites.

For they are all what we honor the highest.

They are all the real troublemakers.

And even though I was one of those for whom the trouble was made, its not an issue since one prankster has got to appreciate the art of another.

And meanwhile, its time for the game to begin."

The whistle was blown. Both teams flew to take their positions.

And the stadium was stunned silence.

What the hell was Harry doing?

"Oh Boy!" Lee said. " It always had to be that kind of a match. One where the commentator gets speechless.

Harry has started with his weirdness already.

Right in the middle of the field, not up in the air, but almost touching the ground, he is hanging on his broom.

Upside down."

" That's right baby." Harry said to himself as even the opposition stayed for a moment to absorb this novelty. " That's where the enemy's gate is. Down, Down, Down. "

Lee continued his own commentary" The entire first year team is entirely unaffected, maybe they are so used to the craziness by now that looking at their captain hanging upside down near the ground looks entirely sensible. So they don't question why isn't their captain not flying high, seeking the snitch and generally trying to win the match.

Talking of which, its not like the team is behaving usually either. Thanks to Harry's weird tactic, Hermione's very off 'take off' went virtually unnoticed. There is no way that she is going to be flying around.

In fact, she and Goyle have gone and taken still position in the air near their own goal post.

What is going on with this team?"

...

"Their formation has two anomalies. The seeker and the beaters are being unorthodox." Six members of senior years heard the voice of Wood in their ears.

Wood was thankful to Harry, for having taken away the commentary from Lee earlier. It showed a perfect way of communicating with the players. Ventriliquo.

And he knew that in this match, against the tactics of Harry, co-ordination and quick response would be the most crucial change.

" Roger, Davies and Derrick, check Hermione and Goyle to see what they have got.

But our clear priority is Harry. We don't know what is going on with him and we can't afford surprises with snitch.

I will try to figure out his plan, meanwhile Fred and George, start with your attack on him. Have fun."

The three chasers began tussiling with the Draco and Patils. It was surprising to see them play decently. At least, it wasn't going to be a cake walk.

Davies took the first hold of quaffle and he flew fast forward.

The field was clear, there was Neville keeping at the end and before that there were Goyle and Hermione just idling lazily in the air a little distance ahead, bouncing off a bludger between them.

They had taken a bludger? When? And was it legal to shuttle it between themselves like that?

When accelerating, something happens to the brain, Davies believed. As if the thinking process accelerates too.

He knew that they will be attacking him with the bludger they seem to have kidnapped by their tactic. They must have practiced hard for this. Matching their hand speed and broom distance to ensure that bludger doesn't change direction midway.

It was sort of innovative to control a bludger like that. But all he had to do was dodge.

It was too simple.

Davies moved with grace and furious elegance. Goyle and Hermione didn't budge an inch from their spots.

Hermione pointed wand somewhere in other direction and said something.

Distraction. Davies noted. Using wand was not illegal in a match if it wasn't being used on other players. Harry must have devised some distracting tactic out of it.

Do not look there but at the bludger, Davies reminded himself.

And when the shuttling bludger reached Goyle, he this time shot it in the direction of Davies.

Good aim. Too close.

Davies swerved. He was used to such attacks.

The bludger travelled harmlessly behind him.

And then..

...

Weasleys hunted down a bludger in no time, just as the bludger was trying to hunt them down.

And their first strike began.

" Bad choice Harry" George said.

" Being so steady. " Fred said.

" And so near the ground." George completed and hit a bludger towards him.

The bludger traveled with murderous speed towards Harry. George hadn't held anything back.

Harry kept watching them from his upside down position near the ground.

Entire Hogwarts in the ground was watching to see who would draw the first blood. And if Harry didn't move soon, he would be the first blood.

Harry did move, his hand. And he snapped his fingers.

...

Davies was rushing towards the goal post as only bludgerless beaters remained in his way. No more obstacles.

And then.. something hit him hard. The bright blue sky in front of him suddenly discovered night. Everything blacked out.

...

There was a collective gasp in the stadiums.

" Unbelievable." Lee was shouting without raising his voice " What did we just see? What on earth was that?

George shot the bludger towards Harry. And the bludger stopped midway. And then turned back.

It turned back on its own. As if it was scared of Harry or something.

Just what kind of magic is going on here?"

Chapter 18: Game's Ender Part I

" Draco. " Harry said, using Ventriliquo too. " We are going to enter phase two. No problem from Wood's side, is there?"

" Not really" Draco replied " Except that he is a legilimens."

"What?" Harry couldn't help but be surprised at this piece of info.

" Not a trained one though. Maybe Wood doesn't even know that he is a legilimens, he perhaps thinks he just has an intuition for such things.

That's why he makes such an excellent keeper."

" How did you figure he was a legilimens." Harry asked.

" Dad made me do a bit of training with some legilimens, just so I could recognize them.

I got a weird sensation when we made the first goal attempt. It didn't take me long to recall what that sensation meant. Once I knew that Wood was reading our minds and attacks, all I had to do was to apply a double blind. I tell both Padma and Parvati that the next pass is going to them and I stay at the back, either making the pass to one of them or going for the goal myself. Wood meanwhile just gets contradictory messages.

It confuses the hell out of him.

Mr. Wood doesn't even know what his problem is." Draco concluded.

"Excellent. That's some good tactic.

So time for phase B it is then." Harry said and terminated the spell.

He shot forward, the bludger still followed him from some distance. He was flying towards his own goal post .

This was particularly hard since Fred and George were without bludgers and had decided to use themselves as human bludgers, flying waywardly to provide worst obstacle. If they came too close, then Harry would have lost the bludger.

However, the one point that Harry had on his side was that he was flying in an unexpected direction.

By now, everybody knew that he could throw the bludger behind him by just swerving. They all expected him to use it again on Cedric .

They didn't expect him to throw it on his own keeper. Neville.

"This has got to be a tough day on Madam Hooch out here." Lee's voice said " Harry hasn't broken any rules as yet, but he sure seems to be trying rather hard. Is it ok to bludger your own keeper?

Is that betting site still on without my knowledge, and has Harry made a bet against his team? For that would be the only sane explanation of this behaviour.

Wait a minute.." Lee stopped in his commentary.

A small but unmistakable thump went across the stadium.

" I was just talking about inexplicable behaviour. Now would somebody tell me what on Earth is Neville doing?

Its true that the defense strategy of First years has worked so well that the quaffle has reached Neville only once till now.

But now it seems he has abandoned his keeper duties altogether.

He is.. I have no I idea what he is doing. If somebody knows, please tell me."

Nobody had the faintest idea.

Harry returned to his upside down position near the ground, but nobody was paying attention to him any longer.

They were looking at Neville who had put the bludger thrown at him through the goal hoop, and as the bludger boomranged back, he stopped it by the side of the hoop and his own broom. He then pushed the bludger by his hands, it traveled horizontally in the air and then landed with a thump on the hoop again. From the ground, it looked like the bludger was just repeatedly hitting the hoop.

Madam Hooch had to check the rules regarding that. Could a keeper really touch a bludger?

But then bludgers were meant to throw off players. If players throw them off in stead, then the rule book had nothing to say against that.

On the other hand, the other keeper was frantically trying to think things out. This was the most acute pressure Wood had ever felt.

" Cedric we need to finish this game. Don't pay attention to Neville's antics or what Harry did, just keep on looking for.." Wood suddenly stopped mid sentence.

" Fred, George. Cover Harry" He nearly shouted as he got hold of another puzzle piece.

" How? He is not even flying, just hovering upside down again." Fred asked.

" I mean cover him literally." Wood replied urgency rising in his voice " What we are seeing right now, all these things are just diverting our attention. The key to this game is still Potter.

I finally figured out why Harry is hanging upside down.

The main skill of a seeker is to seek the snitch and they usually search the various parts of the sky for that periodically by constantly moving.

Potter has just eliminated that requirement.

By being near the ground, and looking up, he could get a full view of all the sky without even moving.

The fact that sky is bright will only help him look out for snitch more easily when it shines against the clear blue background.

That's why one time he left the position, he immediately was able to locate snitch."

" Woah." Fred cut Wood in between.

" We are off." George said and the twins began a dangerously fast descent.

" Hover exactly over him. Stay as near to him as possible or it would still be possible for him to get a good view by slight movements." Wood said and cut off Ventriliquo.

In the next blink, Padma swept over him and scored a goal.

" 50-0" Lee shouted. " Super Keeper Wood has let in another goal. Just how many unprecedented events are we going to see in this game?

And as I announce this, Weasleys have again reached towards the ground. Are we going to see the third round of Weasleys vs. Harry here?"

" Hi again Harry" Fred said as he and George obstructed Harry's view.

Harry grinned.

" So you figured this out too? Most impressive." Harry said.

" What are going to do now?" George said.

" Can't wait to see?" Fred asked.

" Do you know about Dynamic visual acuity? I discovered that mine is good." Harry asked back.

" What?"

" Its.. Never mind, I shouldn't be keeping my eyes off snitch even for few seconds. So this is what's going to happen. I will be moving randomly on my plane. Let's see if you guys can keep up."

And with these words, Harry disappeared sideways.

With uncanny ease, Fred and George moved too. Harry changed his directions again, and so did they. And then again.

"Third round it is." Lee said " I Can't even tell you why on Earth are they doing this, or who is winning out here. It seems like somebody has tied them up together or something, How are they moving so randomly at this speed? Just following them seems to give me a headache.

Or is this headache because of that sound, that constant banging that Neville is doing with that hole he has got up there." Lee said and immediately checked around to see if McGonagall is approaching him angrily already.

But nobody really cared about that right now, all eyes were looking at Neville as the thumping sound finally stopped. Goyle and Hermione moved from their position for the first time since the beginning of the game. Just to be sure that they weren't in the way of the falling hoop. It had finally broken after Neville had made the bludger constantly attack it.

Madam Hooch was checking up on the rule book with an anxious look on her face.

What happens when a keeper 'defends' himself from the bludger by using the goal post, keeps on doing it and eventually breaks one of the goal posts?

Was somebody really mad enough to write that rule?

The hoop fell on the ground and bounced once to leave behind a cloud of dust that slowly rose up and dispersed. Madam Hooch still couldn't find any penalty to give to Neville. And an entire stadium was silent.

Till there was a thumping noise once again.

" One down." Neville said as he put the bludger through another hoop " Two to go."

Chapter 19: Game's Ender Part II

" Davies, Flint, Derrick" Wood shouted intructions in near panic " forget quaffle, look for snitch"

" Snitch?" Flint asked back " We can't touch the snitch, it would mean forfeiting the game."

" I am not asking to capture it. Just locate it." Wood said " And then inform Cedric of the whereabouts through Ventriliquo."

Flint hovered in his position for a while, unable to think of any problem.

" Now Move!" Wood shouted. The trio dispersed.

"Harry." Draco's voice reached Harry " It seems that senior chasers are all seekers now. You want us too to look for snitch, it seems that Weasleys are giving you hard time there."

"They are giving me tough time here." Harry said " But then I expected that from them. I have been practicing these random moves since past one month. They haven't. So in spite of their best, they are slowly loosing the edge, it is becoming easier to keep track of the snitch. In fact, 4 seekers will work further in our favour."

"Right. Now that you say it, I can see how." Draco replied " So what should we do now?"

" Isn't it obvious, with chasers gone off chase, it's a free field for you. Attack, Attack and Attack."

" Music to my ears. Over and out." Draco said and ended the spell.

Padma, Parvati and Draco flew in a circle that faced a lone figure of Wood now.

" Are you really ready for this Wood?" Draco asked " Taking a relentless attack from us, with no chasers on your side? It would be like earning limitless fouls, but even in case of a foul only one player gets to shoot. This is 3 times worse on you. Even on the best of your days you won't be able to take that."

" I won't be." Wood said " But this game is going to end any second now anyway. Are you sure your score would matter by then?"

"Let's find out." Draco said and threw the quaffle. A three way continuous attack on Wood had begun.

The score moved rapidly. And then there was that familiar sound once again.

Another dust cloud rose. Another hoop had fallen.

At the same moment, Parvati scored the 120th point. The three way undivided attacks were really becoming too much for Wood to handle.

"Wood" A voice came to him on Ventriliquo.

" Derrick? You found the snitch" Wood asked, a note of excitement coming in his voice.

" No." Derrick replied.

" Then why are you talking with me? I am already in the middle of this. Get going find the snitch." Wood said.

Draco scored the 130th point. It was almost as if the three of them were taking turns now.

"What's the use?" Derrick replied.

Wood saved the next throw from Padma. He needed to concentrate, Derrick wasn't letting him.

" What the hell you mean what is the use. Get going and search for the snitch." Wood shouted.

" We have already lost this game. Let's at least pay them back." Derrick said.

" Are you crazy Derrick? We have lost the game? Not really, but if you don't do your job, then we might." Wood said while saving another throw.

" Let's foul against them." Derrick said as if he couldn't hear wood at all.

Draco made the 140th point.

" We have got to preserve our dignity Wood. Don't you see it? That's what this whole match is about." Derrick said. " Wood? Can you hear me?"

It took him few seconds to realize that Wood had long before cut the connection. He was determined to delay further score, to give as much time to Cedric as possible for winning the game.

" Cedric." An excited voice of Davies came in.

Cedric didn't need another hint, he realised that Davies had found the snitch. He turned in the air as if a gust had blown him and instantly took off. He could see in a distance, Davies pointing in a direction.

And there it was, the Snitch.

"Padma scores the 150th point." Lee was announcing " And with the third hoop nearly gone too, it seems that Senior years' victory chance has gone away completely."

"It doesn't matter." Thought Cedric as he flew full speed towards the snitch. " A tie would be fine. I just need to get there before the next goal."

As soon as Cedric started chasing the snitch, Davies and Flint had already taken off to their own goal post to help Wood stopping the 160th point. They were now all playing for a tie.

Cedric stole a glance at the goalpost as he was flying. All the three of first year chasers took off as senior chasers approached. The goal won't be happening immediately.

Cedric would be able to catch the snitch before the 160th point. He extended his hands to catch the snitch.

And the snitch disappeared.

"Did it happen on its own?" Lee's voice was announcing " Or did sudden lights that came from Harry's wand were responsible for it.

It looked like he casted something like multiple Lumos Maxima at the same time, the lights spread in all the directions and all the team players went to those lighted spots immediately except Hermione, who presumably just couldn't fly very well. Even the attacking trio of Draco, Padma and Parvati dropped the chance of their 160th point to follow the light.

I somehow don't think that it was coincidence. But what happened just now, only Harry and his team might know. We will need to wait for the answer about how they made the snitch disappear, if they did.

And meanwhile it is here.

Neville has dismantled the third hoop. "

And for the third time the stadium watched a goal post go down.

" They have finally done it." Lee said " First years have now made it impossible for the seniors to score.

In turn it looks like all the senior chasers are now back in the game to prevent the 160th point. They aren't even trying to score now, I mean of course they aren't, their main aim apparently is to not let the first years have the quaffle.

They are still fighting for a tie. This could take time.

Wait a minute, I correct myself. It looks like this won't take time." Lee said "Look who has just joined the party."

Goyle was shooting his way through the first years, and just behind him was Neville who was making the bludger chase him as if he had it tied up from the end of his broom from some invisible cords.

And just before he reached the crowd in the air, he swerved away just like Harry had previously. The bludger shot in the air and hit Derrick who instantly flew back under the force.

A moment's confusion was created and in that moment Draco rose up in the air picking the quaffle dropped by Derrick and throwing it just from above Wood's blind spot. It passed clean.

160th point was scored.

Down below Harry stopped his zig zag moments.

It was as if some machinery suddenly stopped. No player in the stadium was moving any longer.

" Finally" Harry said " Its over."

Chapter 20: Disobedience

"Can I take over the mike?" Harry's voice said to Lee.

" Boy, you are getting good with this Ventriliquo thing.

Sure thing, take over, there are plenty of things we want explained. What the hell had you been doing this entire match? How did you make the snitch disappear, or the bludgers follow you as if charmed? And so much that I will need to make a list.

Just what magic were you using out there? " Lee asked.

Harry's voice then took over the mike

" Magic?

Oh yeah, we used a powerful spell. Rinsio.

Dobby, the house elf taught it to us. He must be here somewhere with SPHEW members right now. Thanks for it Dobby.

It's a really useful spell. Cleans up all the stains on your cloak in no time. Particulaly useful for the blood stains that our cloaks would have after all the tests we conducted on bludgers.

For we knew that the rule book said that bludger is supposed to be random. That 'If left to their own device, the bludger would attack the closest player.' Quidditch through the ages, page 22. Yeah, I even remember the page number now. Did we read that one single line infinite times or what.

Asking ourselves questions like what would happen if two players are equally close to a bludger at the same time. What about 3 then?

Gathering the data about speed of the bludger, its turning frequency etc. etc.

We didn't cast any magic on bludgers. We just understood it.

And thanks Mrs. Pomfrey for mending me and Neville every single day as we pursued our line of curiosity.

And we felt compelled to find out these possibilities by ourselves, since while its true that we were playing a game, we weren't playing somebody else's game.

We weren't doing things just because that's how people have been doing them for hundreds of years. Or had been copying for hundreds of years.

For after all, this game was all about age. About assumption that older is better. About absorption of Dragon and Sunshine in the senior year armies just because they were born a few years ago.

And if anything sums it all up, its that snitch that was never the part of this game. That became a part when a power crazy bureaucrat disrupted the game and used his influence to change it according to his whim.

And nobody questioned it.

And by nobody, I mean you.

Your objective was to over come the opponents, our objective was to overcome the assumptions.

You wanted to be better, we wanted to be good.

Good on our own terms. True to our own objective.

To not see the world with a second hand imagination. "

Harry went silent with these words. Few in the crowd were paying close attention to all the things spoken and unspoken, while most were just noticing that their beliefs were being questioned.

Harry continued, " Most of you are still looking around to see what others are thinking. But then I wasn't planning to end this with an appeal to your rationality.

As I said the objective is not to overcome the opponents, but to overcome assumptions.

Rather than asking you to play the game without snitch, I will just make it irrelevant.

And to do that, I will explain the last mystery of the game.

Do you remember the time when Cedric just missed catching the Snitch and tying the game? You didn't think my spell at that time was a coincidence did you?

The thing is, we didn't just study bludgers. We also studied the snitch.

We found that they are almost opposites of each other. While bludger senses the players and tries to hit them, the Snitch senses the players and tries to escape from them.

That's why it is usually found high up or near the ground, since most players are in the middle level. That is why it is also frequently found near the toes or ears of the players, since that is their blindspot.

So the trajectory of a snitch can be said to be near negative to that of a bludger.

After knowing that, and finding out the details, all I had to do was this..

Lumos Maximus Multiplus.

Snitchus Calculus." Harry said the spell out aloud.

Five shots of lights emerged from Harry's wand at once and went to different locations in air.

Every player in the first year team took off at once to position of the lighted spots. Only two players didn't move, Harry who was still speaking and Hermione who just preferred hovering.

" And with just five players " Harry said " We have changed the player density of the ground. The snitch will now have to find a new location to hide, and by the base of calculations, it would be there. "

Harry pointed a finger. Just above the head of Harry and other players, the snitch fluttered its wings silently. Ready to be caught in a single swoop.

Yet nobody moved to take it.

" It will move in about five to ten seconds. Want to do a count-up?

Never mind, it has moved already to second optimum location. We can move to catch it , but rather than that I will just bring it up again.

Lumos Maximus Multiplus.

Snitchus Calculus

Continuus. " Harry said . And once again the five players swiftly moved to the new positions indicated by the light spots.

" There." Harry pointed to the snitch that once again was visible. " It is now visible again there. Worse, it is now predictable. My last spell will keep telling the team where to move. And as long as others are not flying too far away, that snitch will keep coming back to the same spot.

Anybody who knows how this spell works can easily catch the snitch.

And I will be posting the details of this spell on Floo Book by tonight.

Snitch wouldn't be part of this game any longer. Not if anybody wants to play it for more than 5 seconds."

A spell bound crowd kept seeing the snitch disappear, the lights change, the players move and snitch appear again. With precision, it fluttered on that exact spot.

Everybody in the stadium understood this pretty clearly; snitch was gone. Harry could have won the game anytime, could have had the first year armies back to their dormitories and victory parties after like first 5 seconds of the game.

But he played this crazy game, just to show the possibilities of the game without snitch?

" You think you know it all, don't you?" a voice contacted Harry through Ventriliquo.

"Derrick?" Harry said as he recognized the voice.

" You want to know the difference between first years and seniors? Its simple. We are bigger.

All your arrangements mean nothing. I will just knock out players of yours one by one. The game is not over yet, it would just count as a foul. Score extra points if you want to.

For that's all you can do. You got to gloat just now because Wood wouldn't listen to reason. Wouldn't foul against you first years. I will show you how the real game would have gone. I am not afraid of you Harry." Derrick said.

Harry located Derrick, he was about as far from Harry as Harry was from ground.

" That's because you are too stupid. But I promise you, if you do something like that, I will teach you to be afraid of me." Harry's cold voice said to Derrick.

" Whom to knock off the broom first? Whom? Whom?" Derrick said without paying attention. " Oh yeah, that little red haired sphew who doesn't know how to fly." And Derrick zoomed forward at full speed "She is going down. And there is nothing you can do to save her. You can't reach me on time even with maximum speed of your broom. Isn't that right?"

"No." Harry said in a quick resolution.

His hands moved and he shifted the weight effortlessly. In a moment his broom was pointing at an angle in the sky. It was an absolutely graceful display of flight control.

And then.. he jumped down.

...

Derrick was zooming towards Hermione. She had seen him but it didn't matter. She wouldn't be able to escape with her pathetic flying skill.

Nobody would interrupt this revenge. Everybody was far off, even Harry couldn't reach him until and unless he learned how to apparate in Hogwarts grounds.

Just then, he heard a sound of puff. Somebody grabbed him and everything in front of his blacked out.

" You got to be kidding me?" Derrick shouted " Did you actually learn how to apparate within Hogwarts grounds, Harry?"

He wrestled with the hands gripping his face to remove them. It was then he realized that the hands were too thin even for a first year.

He freed his eyes from the grip and saw that he was facing a little puny house elf.

"No." that creature said in a voice that reminded Derrick of last message of Harry.

For a moment Derrick panicked. But then something within him reminded him that there was no need to panic. He was facing a house elf after all. He didn't need to use force. Just an order would do.

" Get off me house elf." Derrick ordered to the struggling house elf.

The house elf didn't move.

What was happening? How could it have refused a direct order?

" Get off me, now!" Derrick shouted, a panic rising within him.

His hand prised his eyes free from the grip a little more and he found himself looking within round eyes of deep green.

That eye gazed back at him with a chilling look. As if to an unasked question, the elf answered.

" Dobby would not let anyone harm Ms. Hermione." Dobby said.

Derrick could have sworn that Dobby's pupil got narrower and scarier with each and every word.

Then suddenly there was an impact and his broom was gone from under him and he was falling. Falling upwards.

...

Few seconds ago.

Harry was falling down after he jumped from his broom.

" Fly. Full speed." He shouted to his broom that aimed upwards towards sky, at an angle and then he shouted once more "FRED! GEORGE!"

His body continued falling towards the ground. Madam Pomfrey can't mend scattered brains, he reminded himself of that fact as he saw the ground getting closer.

And then two arms grabbed him from the sides. His descent slowed down and then he started moving upwards. Harry looked up at the Weasleys.

" And we thought" Fred said

" That our jumping on a still broom was crazy." George said with great admiration in his voice.

" Had to do it." Harry said. " A broom's maximum speed falls with more weight on it. And it increases when the weight is removed.

Derrick was right, I couldn't have reached him on time. But a broom without rider could."

" So to save Hermione from falling down to her death, you fall down to your own death?" George asked.

" No way." Harry answered " I knew you would catch me."

They all looked up to see the impact of the Harry's broom with Derrick. There were some odd movements there, and a greenish blur.

" Now stop doing this Derrick." Cedric ventriliquoed with snitch in his hand" The game is over. Its their win."

Derrick's voice came back but it didn't seem to be addressing Cedric.

" Get off me, now!" Derrick said.

And then everybody around heard another voice , one that was cold and fiery at the same time " Dobby would not let anyone harm Ms. Hermione."

"Dobby?" Harry noticed with a wonder.

Then there was the crash. Harry's broom got entangled in Derrick's cloak , lifting him higher up in the sky.

Hermione had seen Derrick coming. She was ready with her wand to hex him the moment he came in the range.

But just as she was about to fire her spell, the crash happened. She breathed a sigh of relief. Everything was safe.

And then she was knocked out of her broom.

Derrick's rider-less broom had continued to travel towards her. She should have foreseen that, she thought. She should have been able to avoid that and now she just had few seconds to kick herself mentally as the ground rushed close. Maybe Dumbledore would save her. He wouldn't just let a student fall to death, would he?

Her fall stopped.

She was hanging in air by her cloak's neck, which was being held by.. " Dobby?" Hermione shrieked with relief as she looked up at Dobby who was now flying on her just abandoned broom. The sun behind gave him a halo and completed the glorious scene.

Somewhere in the back of her thankful mind, she was making a mental note to burn her copy of 'Hogwarts: A History' that talked about how 'people' can't apparate within Hogwarts castle. So even the wisest didn't think of house elves as 'people', did they?

She was the only person with those thoughts though. The rest of Hogwarts was almost violently celebrating the end of this phenomenal game and above all they were celebrating the final image as Dobby held on to Hermione's hand and didn't let her fall.

Somewhere in the distance Draco was hearing Patil twins coo at that scene "How unlike his master" they said. And Draco couldn't help but shudder at the thought that from now onwards he was forever going to be remembered as 'The Drop Lord'.

Chapter 21: Disobedience Part II

Harry was rather relieved when the crowd focused their entire energy on throwing Dobby up and down in the air. Besides, Harry genuinely felt that Dobby deserved that celebration. Though Harry still didn't get how Dobby was able to disobey a direct order from Derrick.

" Nice game Harry" Fred and George said as they approached him.

" Thanks. No need to say, but the same goes for you too guys." Harry grinned " And yeah, one more thing. I will be posting the spell for snitch control on your Floo Book. You guys won't have any problem with that move would you?"

Two jaws dropped and four eyes opened a bit larger than they were used to.

" 'Our' Floo Book. How did you know that we.."

".. were together the 'Gutenberg of Gossip', the 'Life Eater' etc. ?

I helped Zabini hack the site to make a betting page, remember? I couldn't help but find out a few details about the originators." Harry said.

"You can't tell anybody about this." Fred said in a hush.

" We have plans for this thing. What you see now, it's just a prototype." George whispered.

" I am not telling anyone. But seriously, if only Winklevoss brothers knew that some other twins did this. Ha ha ha." Harry laughed and as the laughter died he found out that he was the only one laughing.

" I don't know why I just said that." Harry replied " Particularly because according to our timeline Winklevoss twins wouldn't even get involved in the matter for ages." Harry completed the sentence in a single breath knowing that he will hear silence once again in reply.

" And no, I don't know why I said that either. Popular theory is that this is what happens to you if you spend too much time with Dumbledore." Harry said and finally there was some empathy in twins' eyes. 'Ah, another victim of our crazy headmaster' they must have thought with some pride.

" Talking about Dumbledore, look who is coming to congratulate you." George said and looked back. Harry knew the answer without turning back.

"We are leaving. Don't you dare get any weirder while we are gone." Fred said and the twins walked off.

Harry took a deep breath. Was he prepared for the conversation with Headmaster finally? Could anybody ever be prepared to take on that madness voluntarily? Harry let his deep breath free again. He had to do this. He turned around and found himself staring up in electric blue eyes behind half moon spectacles.

" Congratulations Harry. That was an interesting game in deed. You managed to achieve your twin objectives of removing the snitch and stopping the inter year wars." Dumbledore said.

" Not really professor." Harry said. He took a second before beginning to speak again, but then it was all long planned, he couldn't stop the execution now " Stopping the Inter Year Wars was never my objective. I rather thought that it was a great idea.

Please continue with it. Let superior teams absorb the inferior teams.

And by that of course I mean disband the armies of the senior generals who were in today's game. And let us, the winnders command them.

Won't that be a better form of Inter Year Wars. Wasn't that the whole purpose?"

Harry said and waited with his fists involuntarily clenched. He knew that Dumbledore would give a reply that he perhaps won't even be able to understand , let alone counter. But he had to counter it. He had to make sure that his version of Inter Year Wars happened, for it would give him the real training, that of commanding those who were considered grown ups. All he had to do was to somehow win this argument with Dumbledore.

'OK.' Dumbledore said "Congrats once again." And he turned back to go away.

" What?" Harry couldn't suppress that question " You just agreed? You just Agreed?"

" Sure." Dumbledore turned back and smiled " After all this is just the first stage of your game. I will get plenty of time to screw with you later on."

Harry blinked. Twice. Headmaster was crazy, but since when did he start being that funky? And more importantly..

" Fist stage of my game?" Harry asked tentatively.

" You think its not obvious? Did you think, Mr. Takamura, that when you threatened to announce your predictions to a stadium full of people, I would believe that as an attempt to get leverage?" Dumbledore looked down from his height at Harry with an unflinching kindness.

Harry was getting nervous. He couldn't afford that conversation to continue. He wasn't yet ready to take on Dumbledore at such an early stage.

"But it doesn't matter." Dumbledore said, "I am in a good mood.

After all, not everyday one sees two successful revolts against the precedents.

I will leave now Harry, but let me complete the final duty of an old wizard to impart some parting gems of wisdom.

'It is our choices, Harry, that show what we truly are, far more than our abilities.'

Though I wasn't really supposed to say that until the end of your second year.

But today as we once again see the future change, who knows if there would be a second year at all. And that line seemed like an important thing to tell." After saying that Dumbledore smiled for few seconds while seeing an expression of dumbfounded-ness on Harry's face that seemed to be universal amongst audience of Dumbledore.

Harry meanwhile was trying to remember these sentences verbatim. Was Dumbledore really being crazy once again, or was he telling him something about the nature of prophecies and time travel? But then, he again reminded himself not to take the bait. There was a clear information asymmetry here and at this stage he was not yet ready to go for that conversation.

" You said" Harry found himself asking something altogether different " that there were two successful revolts against the precedents today. Which was the other one?"

Dumbledore laughed.

" Nice question to pick Harry, out of all the possibilities. Truly." He said. " Is there any other question that you haven't answered yourself today? Like how exactly a friend of yours overcame his very fundamentals of nature in order to save another friend?"

And with these words, Dumbledore finally walked away.

Harry turned towards Dobby. Indeed, how did he manage it?

Dobby had by now escaped the cheerful mob and was standing by himself.

" Dobby." Harry walked up to him.

Dobby didn't move even slightly. Harry walked a bit further and his shadow fell over Dobby. With a start, he comically jumped and looked up to Harry.

" Harry Potter Sir." He said with a delighted expression.

" Dobby, thanks a lot for saving Hermione.

But if I may ask, how did you ignore Derrick's direct orders?" Harry asked.

" Eh?" Dobby seemed confused and then his eyes brightened " Just a minute Potter sir, Dobby can't hear you right now."
Dobby raised his hands, and in a movement that was all too familiar to Harry, Dobby snapped his fingers.

Two small bursts of smoke appeared near Dobby's ears. And an extra magically grown skin disappeared from his earholes.

Harry found that he nearly stopped breathing for a second. His skin rustled with the sensation of goosebumps.

He finally understood what Dobby had done. So simple, yet so remarkable.

He didn't just close his ears to not hear the command, he in effect found a will to try and go against his very nature to obey.

Harry was just proven wrong. But he felt that he could shout with joy. And keep on shouting.

" Sorry, Potter sir. I had magically closed my ears to not hear whatever Derrick ordered Dobby to do.

What was Potter sir saying?" Dobby asked.

I was wrong about you Dobby. Harry wanted to say. I was wrong about House elves in general. How could I have been so blind? You did overcome what I supposed to be your fundamental nature, and all by yourself.

Hermione was right about you. And I am so thankful for that Dobby.

" Mr. Potter sir?" Dobby looked a bit anxious as Harry just stood there saying nothing and looking at him.

"Nothing." Harry finally said. " I just wanted to say how thankful I am to you Dobby, for… for what you did today.

And yeah" Harry added as an afterthought " What book had you been reading this past month?"

" Missy Hermione gave that wonderful book to me." Dobby said and his tone had shifted from respect to that of pride " Life and times of Frederick Douglass."

" Frederick Douglass. But, of course." Harry said. " Thanks once again Dobby. I do owe you" And he walked away before Dobby could have started with his protests.

...

Far up in the sky Derrick was clinging on for his dear life as a broom kept on taking him higher. His attempts to turn it back had proven useless.

" Stop" Harry's voice came through Ventriliquo and finally the broom stopped.

" There is something I want to say to you Derrick" Harry's voice said.

Derrick didn't respond. He was afraid. Very afraid. He didn't want to hear anything. He would do whatever Harry asked him to do right now, if only Harry would let him down.

And then Harry's voice continued after, what seemed to be, a moment's struggle. "And what I want to say is, sorry."

Static stopped in Derrick's mind. Harry was apologizing to him?

" Don't get me wrong. I am not apologizing for what I did right now. I wouldn't have let you attack Hermione.

But that said, I did provoke you in the earlier game when I called you fat. I did humiliate you.

Whatever your actions might have been in the past, nothing then warranted that treatment.

I didn't apologize earlier because I just thought of you as a bully.

But today I surprisingly discovered my own invisible assumption that people do not change. And today I also saw it proven completely wrong.

So I apologies for that one act.

And I hope you and I will change for the better too." Harry concluded and on his next command the broom containing an inscrutable Derrick turned back.